var questionArray = [{

    question: 'How many seasons of friends are there?',
    choices:[ '5','6','9','10',],
    answer:'10', 
},
{
    question: 'Who is the host of Americas Next top Model?',
    choices:['Paris Hilton', 'Tyra Banks','RuPaul',	'Heidi Klum', ],
    answer:'Tyra Banks'
},
{   
    question: 'The show (Insecure) is based on works in what other entertainment medium?',
    choices: ['Drawing', 'Music', 'Webseries', 'Tweets'],
    answer: 'Webseries',
},
{
    question: 'What is the name of the college on "Dear White People"?',
    choices:['Winchester College','Arial College',	'Barden University',	'Harvard',],
    answer: 'Winchester College',
},
{  
    question: 'What cop show does Andy Samberg star in?',
    choices:['Chicago PD','Law and Order','Brooklyn Nine-Nine', 'Criminal Minds', ],
    answer: 'Brooklyn Nine-Nine',
},
{
    question: 'The TV show "Game of Thrones" is based on a novel by which author?',
    choices: ['George R. R. Miller',	'Arthur Miller',	'Ian Fleming',	'Thomas Harding',],
    answer: 'George R.R. Miller',
},
{
    question: 'What is the name of the basketball team on the show "One Tree Hill"?',
    choices: ['The Eagles',	'The Ravens',	'The Raiders',	'The Phantoms', ],
    answer: 'The Ravens',
},
{
    question: 'Ted Mosby and Marshall Eriksen are both characters on which show?',
    choices: ['How I Met Your Mother','One Tree Hill','Community','Lie To Me',],
    answer: 'How I Met Your Mother',

},
{
    question: 'What show does Courtney Cox star in?',
    choices:['Once Upon a Time','Glee',	'Cougar Town',	'Castle',],
    answer: 'Cougar Town',

},
{
    question: 'In which city do Ross and Rachel Get married in?',
    choices:['Los Angeles',	'Paris','Las Vegas','New York City', ],
    answer: 'Las Vegas',
},
];





